<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Comedy Africa</string>
    <string name="accueil">Home</string>
    <string name="plus">More</string>
    <string name="favoris">Our Selection</string>
    <string name="populaire">Popular</string>
    <string name="popular_humorist">Comedians</string>
    <string name="new_videos">Most Recent</string>
    <string name="comediens">Comedians</string>
    <string name="see_all">See All</string>
    <string name="next_video">More Videos</string>
    <string name="vues">vues</string>
    <string name="send_with">Send with</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact Afrimoov</string>
    <string name="review">Be nice, review our app :-)</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="data_usage">Data Consumption</string>
    <string name="remove_ads">Remove Ads</string>
    <string name="more_apps">Other Afrimoov Apps</string>
    <string name="mode_compact_tite">Compact cards</string>
    <string name="mode_compact_message">Pictures won\'t display when this option is selected. Content will load faster and data consumption will be lower.</string>
    <string name="notif_title">Push notifications</string>
    <string name="notif_message">Mange notifications for any Comedian:</string>
    <string name="on">ON</string>
    <string name="off">OFF</string>
    <string name="devise">Watch African comedies for free !</string>
    <string name="autres">More</string>
    <string name="like_app">Do you like the application ?</string>
    <string name="noter">Review</string>
    <string name="annuler">Cancel</string>
    <string name="new_version">New Version is available</string>
    <string name="update">Update</string>
    <string name="discover">Discover</string>
    <string name="teaser_message">Discover the best africans comedians</string>
    <string name="popular_plan">popular</string>
    <string name="month">Month</string>
    <string name="months">Motnths</string>
    <string name="ad_free">Switch to ad-free mode</string>
    <string name="daily_channel_description">"Everyday we send you the most popular videos "</string>
    <string name="daily_channel_name">Videos you must see</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_title">Copyright Declaration</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">"Afrimoov TV respects copyright law. If you believe that a post infringes your copyrights, you may submit to us a notification pursuant to applicable law so that we can solve it as soon as possible. Do not use this procedure for matters unrelated to copyright infringement. Your notification of claimed infringement must include the following information: (1) an electronic or physical signature of the owner or of the person authorized to act on behalf of the owner of the copyright interest; (2) identification of the copyrighted work (or works) that you claim has (or have) been infringed; (3) a description of the material that you claim is infringing, and the location where the original or an authorized copy of the copyrighted work exists (for example, the URL of the page of the website where it is lawfully found; the name, edition and pages of a book from which an excerpt was copied, etc.); (4) a clear description of where the infringing material is located, including as applicable its URL, so that we can locate the material; (5) your name, address, telephone number, and e-mail address; (6) a statement that you have a good-faith belief that the disputed use is not authorized by the copyright owner, its agent, or the law; and (7) a statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the above information in your notice is accurate and that you are the copyright owner or authorized to act on the copyright owner’s behalf. You can report alleged copyright infringement by emailing the above information to afrimoov237@gmail.com  "</string>
    <string name="nouveau">New</string>
    <string name="comedy">comdy</string>
    <string name="today">Today</string>
    <string name="this_week">This week</string>
    <string name="this_month">This month</string>
    <string name="tendances">Trending</string>
    <string name="all">All</string>
    <string name="share_message">"Find more videos with Comedy Africa App ! Click here "</string>
    <string name="connexion_issue">It seems like you have connexion issue</string>
    <string name="reload">Retry</string>
    <string name="privacy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
</resources>